and today i found that home depot
something that turns um regular paint
into spray paint
[Music]
hi welcome to my channel
the j formula i almost forgot that for a
second
so i am creeping
up on a milestone with my youtube
channel
i am so close to 1 000 watch hours
with a measly 74 subscribers
it was 76 but i lost to rit
now i'm down to 74. and
i need a thousand so you do the math
1000 hours 74 subscribers
[Music]
i beseech you subscribe
help us us to make some money i'm
struggling out here in these streets you
don't want me to end up on the pole
trust me you don't want me to end up on
the pole today i wanted to film
i guess kind of a product review slash
diy
here it is the it's called
travel amazing spray system
what i like about this idea is i have
spray painted furniture before thinking
it would be easier than painting and
it's a mess
it can be a mess the paint so i wanted
to try spray painting
this piece of furniture it was actually
the two bootcases that are behind me i
don't know if you can see them
back there and seven or eight
cans of spray paint later it cost me a
fortune i think each spray paint can was
about four dollars five dollars five
times a forty bucks when i could have
just bought one of those
little gideon paint cans and
for what ten bucks ten maybe fifteen
dollars
and you know what the person at home
people advise me they were like
they suggested after i was back for my
my third and fourth because i swore i
was only gonna be four the lady at home
depot the associate was like
hey have you thought about this and i
was like oh this is cool but no i don't
need that i only need two more cans so
to invest in this and then i gotta buy
the paint and i'm not even gonna use
that much paint
no thank you for more tricks later
i wish i would have done this so today
i'm gonna try to see
if it actually is worth the hype
so it comes with an aerosol can
and a glass bottle that holds the paint
i am now going to be adding my
actual paint oh look at me getting all
macgyver
using a piece of foil cupcake foil
holder
as a funnel so i don't get paint
everywhere on my nice
laminate wood floors that is not really
mine because i'm renting
the side of the box has instructions on
how to make
regular paint spray paintable
by diluting it with either water
or paint thinner now i've tried this
before
and it didn't work when i used paint
thinner so now
round two is me trying it with water
[Music]
okay let's see how it goes shake
shake shake shark
[Music]
so we know the aerosol can work
but um
yeah i'm not getting any spray paint
i'm not getting any paint to come out
okay
um maybe i didn't shake it enough
or maybe i didn't add enough paint so
let me add some more paint it does say
one part to two parts water or something
like that
and it's still not
working
i'm not giving up because maybe i'm
doing something wrong
all right it's time for some
troubleshooting i think
maybe the two where the paint is
supposed to go through
is clogged like i said before i did try
this before
by diluting the paint with paint thinner
and it and it didn't work
so maybe some of the paint is dried in
the tube
it does look like the tube is clogged
so i'm using a thumb tacky thing
with a sharp end to unclog it
and this is me feverishly trying to get
the tube unplugged
take two was a hard fail
fail fail more troubleshooting
okay so i am going back to the paint
thinner
and trying that again
but with less paint i think
and you can see the clear separation
between the paint and paint thinner
which kind of tells me that it doesn't
mix but
who knows that's what the box says the
box says
paint thinner and paint and
yeah this is some
okay i'm giving this two thumbs down
i can get paint on my fingers but not on
the actual wood
well it's pretty safe to say that
this was a fail add it to the long list
of fails that i have to endure
in life
i am one that prefers to try
and fail rather than not try at all so
it wasn't a waste i guess i will be
sticking to spray paint cans or
painting the old fashioned way with a
brush